

085692846848 (Mobile) syauri04@gmail.com

Address:

Perum bukit pasundan 2 Jl cijulang, Ds Sukaharja Kec Cijeruk, Kab.Bogor

www.linkedin.com/in/rifanahmad-syauri-497242148

Skills

PHP, Laravel, Codeingiter Jquery, Javascript, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap GSAP, NextJS, NodeJs, REST APIs, Wordpress, LMS Moodle, Mysql

Ε

&

Curriculum Vitae

Rifan Ahmad Syauri 29 April 1995/ 29th

Full-stack Developer at Hijr Studio - Digital Creative Agency Bogor, West Java, Indonesia

Summary

I have several years of experience in programming and website development in Indonesia. I have developed many small to medium-sized web applications using the latest technologies. My experience ranges from building simple single-page websites to complex multi-page enterprise applications.

I have worked on several projects using various frameworks such as Laravel, Codelgniter, Node.js, React.js, and Next.js. In addition, I am an expert in PHP, REST APIs, CSS3, jQuery, and responsive design using HTML and Material Design guidelines.

Experience

Hijr Studio - Digital Creative Agency Full-stack Developer September 2019 - Present (5 years 6 months) Bogor, Indonesia

I have worked on various projects, including creating market places, company profile websites, and web API services for mobile apps. I also helped design database structures for companies' content management systems

PT. Jasa Dan Kepariwisataan Jabar (Perseroda) Web Developer

October 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Bandung, Indonesia

I contributed to the development of the GURILAPS app project (marketplace wisata jawa barat). My role involved creating the web app version and developing REST APIs.

PT Trias Cipta Mandiri - IT Cosultant Full-stack Developer November 2014 - October 2017 (3 years)

Bogor, Indonesia

Here, I worked on several projects, focusing on developing company portal systems for business management.

EGO. Advertising & Design Web Developer May 2013 - November 2014 (1 year 7 months)

Most of my projects focused on creating web designs for clients

PT Bahtera Informatika

Jakarta Utara, Indonesia

and the company itself.

Web Developer

January 2012 - September 2012 (9 months)

Jakarta, Indonesia

This company focuses on providing technology for biometric recognition (face, fingerprints) and graph databases. In this company, I assist in developing systems tailored to client needs.

Education

Universitas Pakuan Bogor Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2014 - 2021) Bogor, Indonesia

SMK WIKRAMA BOGOR

Vocational High School Diploma, RPL · (2010 - 2013)

Bogor, Indonesia